<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>knyL</title><description>I work creating software that solve problems in a simple way, and this place use to share what I learn along the way. The blog will focus on .NET Core and other related technologies. I hope you will gain some knowledge here on knyl.me. See y&apos;all around!</description><link>https://www.knyl.me/</link><item><title>CI/CD for My Own Projects: Ain&apos;t nobody got time for manual deployment, amirite?</title><link>https://www.knyl.me/blog/ci-cd-for-my-small-projects-by-using-github-actions/</link><guid>https://www.knyl.me/blog/ci-cd-for-my-small-projects-by-using-github-actions/</guid><description>As a dev, I usually don&apos;t like to deploy my own projects &apos;cause the whole process takes a lot of time and there&apos;s always the risk of messing things up. But ever since I switched to GitHub Actions CI/CD, I&apos;ve been able to save time, cut down on errors, and concentrate on the real deal - developing my projects. </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Install TimescaleDB on an existing PostgreSQL container</title><link>https://www.knyl.me/blog/install-timescaledb-on-an-existing-postgresql-container/</link><guid>https://www.knyl.me/blog/install-timescaledb-on-an-existing-postgresql-container/</guid><description>I researched TimescaleDB, a powerful database for time-series data. While installing it on an existing container, I encountered a challenge. After experimenting with different methods and configurations, I successfully installed TimescaleDB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Set up Wildcard SSL for Godaddy domain with Let&apos;s Encrypt</title><link>https://www.knyl.me/blog/set-up-wildcard-ssl-for-godaddy-domain-with-lets-encrypt/</link><guid>https://www.knyl.me/blog/set-up-wildcard-ssl-for-godaddy-domain-with-lets-encrypt/</guid><description>Using Certbot to set up SSL for Godaddy domain</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Very First Post</title><link>https://www.knyl.me/blog/the-very-first-post/</link><guid>https://www.knyl.me/blog/the-very-first-post/</guid><description>A new beginning for knyL&apos;s blog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>